# Wajd Al-Ghailani

Orlando, FL | (407) 256-5442 | wajdalghailani123@knights.ucf.edu

#### **EXECUTIVE SUMMARY**

Finance major at the University of Central Florida with three years of extensive volunteer and public speaking experience within social services and other formal platforms. Success in supporting organizational needs through delivery of media coverage. Seeking to expand customer service abilities into the finance industry and gain a deeper understanding of financial and accounting practices. Languages: Fluent in English and Arabic. Computer Skills: Proficient Microsoft Office Suites (Word, PowerPoint, Excel).

#### **EDUCATION**

### University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL

December 2021

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration, Finance (GPA: 3.44)

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL

October 2020-Present

Armor Up Ambassador (Part-time)

 Assit in keeping the UCF campus healthy through reinforcing beneficial behaviors with students such as; face covering, physical distance and COVID Self Checker App

# The Ewing Family Security & Staffing Services, Orlando, FL

**January 2021-Present** 

Sporting Event Staff (Part-time)

- Well versed for exceptional customer service, while remaining friendly and approachable to assist clients and patrons of all backgrounds and group sizes with all of their needs during various events
- Manage and evaluate event security as needed

#### LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE AND ACTIVITIES

#### UCF Volunteer- Orlando, FL

January 2020-Present

Volunteer

• Volunteer in different communities to help serve underrepresented populations such as poor and special needs individuals, providing comfort, guidance, food, and shelter

#### NSLS-Orlando, FL

September 2020-Present

Member

• A member on the national society of leadership and success, where I was nominated by UCF for my academic standing. Communicate with my peers every week to discuss our accomplishments and set new goals

## $Omani\ Student\ Association\ at\ UCF-\ Orlando,\ FL$

August 2019 - Present

- Photographer
  - Maintain and organize all the events for the Omani Student Association that aims to create a sense of ease and comfort for the UCF Omani population while attending UCF
  - Manage social media account for the Omani Student Association, keeping members abreast of networking and social opportunities throughout the semester

#### **Event Management**

**August 2019 – Present** 

 Plan and co-create the National Day for the Omani Student Association successfully bringing a total of 120 students together for a day of activities, events, and community involvement

#### **HONORS**

• President's List (Summer2020), Dean's List (Spring 2020), Dean's List (Fall 2019), Paid Scholarship from the Ministry of Higher Education (Spring 2018 – Present)